goodday
J you been there fishing lately J I
don't go fishing why want you come down
fishing with us I take down I hate
fishing I hate the water how about we go
f for some rocks we're going get some
rocks going some m in the that many
rocks in my head hang on just turn
sideways again we had a bit of light
shining through what
happened 95 tape shows that um if you
have the water yeah um level with the
plate below them get gas just half gas
coming off off the
plate you raise the water above the
plate which means that the plates are
got to be a certain distance you have to
have the plates down enough or you got
to have the sell up enough right what
about if I raise that Center w't do it
why do it what do we got there Joe what
what would you say it
was hate to comment that's up to you no
no you can you're allowed to comment
the what happens is is is the
um your
plates how do I say this your brown
Browns gas hydrogen and oxygen batteries
everything girls they got two plates the
plates do to work you get oxygen off the
positive plate you get hydrogen
supposedly off the negative plate at the
bottom we've discussed this right you
don't matter how high or low you have
the water no matter what electrolyte you
got in that but with um what you might
call neutral
plates the plates are not supposed to
produce in old fashioned science but in
the new fashioned science they do
produce only because you're looking at
them you can see they're producing no
they're not the water's producing yeah
it's coming out of the water yeah but
the water is
producing there's no interacting really
with the plates the water produces now
if you look the 95 tape and everything
else you'll see the glass coffee bottle
with the plates and if you bring the the
water it's on video there and you have
it the water comes up below or level
with the tops of the plates which you
have here the cell produces nearly zero
nothing out of it
yeah you've seen that yep okay and it
only comes off one side of the plate
yeah when it goes up and over it then
spirals down as well when it comes up
over the top a certain level and
everything else which by you adding the
water you find out your level of your
cell because each cell is different
because of width length breadth height
whatever size of plates and everything
else it sets its own level and you got
to have above that level right okay you
got to have airspace above that level
for expansion of water and so that
vacuum don't pull any water down through
the tubes if you're going to pull off
okay I don't care how it is up above or
down or anything else we use this design
right back with Ron Davis with the
center being used as neutral to pull gas
back down to there and everything else
for welders and O
remembered the cells right okay it
emptied the cells okay you're going back
in on yourself well I always getting
sucked in you know
that so the idea hang on hang on he's
smiled what happened there was a little
bit
there the um mate I've missed you for 3
months what's happened yeah the when you
see on the 95 tape and everything else
out there if you've got your water which
is nowhere near going to happen in this
it would be above what this is now
without that in what you got there so
this outside tube has to be a lot longer
than the tubes inside now you bring your
water up with the charge on you'll see
when you get up this is in the coffee
bottle you'll see Jad it now produces
something phenomenal out of the water
and that stuff goes up down as milk it
doesn't break the surface yeah it goes
down to halfway and returns and
something from halfway goes down and
back now that's not coming off the
plates that's happening out of the water
and that produces a hell of a lot more
and that energy is the is um high
powered chip okay I don't play any of
this anymore but that's what it is now
this here won't do that all this is
going to do is empty mosty water and
shut down yourself because below those
plates if the water stays there and
everything else there only going to be
one quarter of what the potential is of
what this machine you know what should
come off right it's not just one quarter
it's only coming off one side of one
plate now it's not the ordinary gases it
is a mixture it's not hydrogen and
oxygen it is a mixture of gases what do
combine okay it's not oxygen coming off
the side walls and hydrogen coming out
the bottom tips like two plates do okay
because you got give me for a second
right
right put it down yeah right
so they can see it if they like they
can't see it I'm not letting them say it
yet whatever huh whatever they're not
allowed to look at it yet don't
look this this is too close there's not
enough water above it's not going to do
too much any your GS you're not going to
give get enough of if you're after gases
energy not enough height SS not enough
it's been drops s and cut both ends and
everything else going black the fame
plates inside got uh pulling the pieces
it's got um it's got tubes in it's got
seams in there you can see and it's
aring through the seams aren't even
lined up no right the plat these rubbers
are pulling to pieces and turning brown
this thing here is arching even though
you say you haven't got power to it this
rubber here black color in the design B
and it's arching back in as that ring
and it's going blue it's arching back in
now where you getting the charges yeah
well doesn't have to be because your
water's electrically connected yeah your
plates are don't even have to it can be
either one or none yeah you're going to
set up a charge factor in the water
because the water turns left and it
turns right you go to Victor shurger
stuff and everything else you go to um
and Victor shows that if the water turns
left and then turns right he puts in the
cups he turns lights on yeah with that
water turning one turning left one
turning right and it doesn't matter
which one and it'll go either way now
your tap water turns left right left
right and everything else and then
change the top it always turn this water
in here is always going to be turning
and rotating there is double charges
within the water do you understand that
without applying
charge so it's a positive negative and a
negative positive
four charges in the water negative
negative and a negative
positive I don't think i' say that
either right you would get that you'll
get things like that if you apply charge
well it's a lot like how you playing
with those magnets before down yeah but
the the you can't call it that see it's
wrong
telling it's wrong telling because the
the charge or comes off water doesn't
match your AC or DC charges positive or
negative North or South Pole doesn't
match it okay yeah even though it might
turn Victor shurger light bulb on but
they just turn they walk up close to it
and it's flipping they put meters in
there meters and everything else and it
changes you understand or it goes
different ways the water turns different
the things sometimes the lights won't
come on and it's still turning the water
yeah they haven't is the water falling
the water is water is dropping but it
doesn't have to fall because out of the
cap or in a in a pipeline or anything
else it still does same thing water
turns and turn this water turns and it
goes two different ways and it'll do it
within its own distance you can't make
it stay in the distance the thing that
you want yeah okay so um you can do
anything you like to try and keep it
turning one way you can't and if you try
to turn it the other way we'll build up
an opposite massive big charge yeah
nearly 10 times because it's got its own
distance understand by going say this
much and then keeping to turning into
the left it may build up one charge this
way and it should be turning itself the
other all by itself you keep it going to
the left that distance there will
recharge but won't be the same as the
because it's got its own distance
fantastic thanks Joe thanks very much
for that much appreciate it